Milestone 3: Physics and Collision

For this milestone, we mostly worked on fixing our game up and resolving previous bugs from the pathfinding milestone, so we weren’t able to do too much physics/collision stuff, but this this should resolved in time for the next presentation.

We worked on debugging the AI (making sure clustering and pathfinding to the centroids works correctly). We also worked on polygon collisions (we’re going to use Tiled Map Editor and create a tile map and an overlaid/underlaid collision layer which details poly lines around our map to solve jagged edges of our game world). We also worked on blowback for when a player hits the edge of our walkable areas, and rendering complex geometry onto the screen (missiles and such).
